Do the talk I guess I walk and talk. Let's walk into the store. Hello everybody. Oh
I don't know. I think it's like
like when I'm like so nice
Then it's like
People just think it's easy to see that
Either be mad at me or never forgive me. I don't understand
the other people
Seems to get through you up. Hello for your joint. Good morning. Hi, Gotti. That's all these people are mad at me
I mean, it's so many and
It's a cute dog, I'll try to show you.
See the dog.
Let's go to the store.
What's up, Charisma?
God, you have to turn that madness into gladness?
I don't know, because some of them are like friends.
Like, I'm not gonna use names, they're so bad.
But there's like a long time mod I had,
and then, you know, I've been through so many ups and downs,
trying to like, you know, maintain the friendship,
and I've always been there, whatever.
They have a friend that I, somebody that they didn't like,
came in, one of them hit him for 30 seconds or something.
Then he gets all mad, and then it just created this whole,
like, night of screaming at each other.
Now, they're mad at me.
That person's probably mad at me.
I apologize.
It was said, oh, take your apologies,
shove it up your block, and, like, go hug a cactus.
So, I mean, I even, like, apologize to that horrible Kate.
You know, it's because I said, you know, probably terrible thing,
but I didn't say anything about her family or anything.
That was somebody else.
But it's like, and then too, that person was like,
one of the, he was like, he was, he was saying that I doxed
Crystal's mom's name on my show.
Well, that was because it was his friendships.
I do care about someone.
I don't know.
There you go.
Let them be mad.
I know, but it's like, I'm going through a hard time right now.
It's like so easy to like, I guess when someone's
deemed unpopular or like, you know, bad or something
and it's easy for everyone to just be bad at me,
it's just kind of, it all doesn't really matter.
Yeah, I think it might be a lower case.
Not sure how, my part is kind of finicky sometimes.
Not sure.
Let me see if I get,
the audio is getting all the same ones,
chords the other day.
Let me see how it does for me.
Let me see, got the exclamation point.
There you go tarot card. There you go. You got the fool, Gotti. Oh my gosh
That's what I look like though
Okay
All right, I am like a little bit like swollen. I guess I'm having scary dreams
I'm having bad dreams about like getting on the boat and like oh I have these dreams about like
Hacking anything and not being able to carry my bags and stuff like that. You got the fool Gotti. I got
Fool's a good in Italy. There's something there's like a saying in Italy
It's like the whole point of life is to be the fool or something like that or the happiest person is the fool
I'm gonna hear about the fool before you go. Well, that means like, you know
Like it's not like it's in the upright, right? And so oops
Take a leap of faith
When I wash our hair today or not. I wash my hair. I wash my hair always
Here's clean. I washed it. That's why it's kind of like an afro
and I took out my brand of it, I was like,
the hair is clean.
And look, and now they have real pictures of everyone else.
They have all these, like a sand band
puts these real pictures up for other people.
And then it's like, all of them are me,
are like these AI of where I'm bald,
and my house is mess.
You're my real hair, it's like, I'm not bald.
I always had this hairline.
It goes kind of far back, but it's not like,
I mean, I have this in the front to make up for that.
I always used to say, that's where my horns go.
My dad had the same hairline.
After 86 years old, he had full head of hair.
Crazy dreams, but we're like,
there was like Nazis or something running after us
and we were all hiding and like,
and then they would come over and then do the kite again
and like, we drew these like kind of like Christmas
kind of like scenes so they wouldn't recognize us.
We pretend we're like the Nativity scene mannequins
or something.
It was just so weird.
And we're in this, like, amusement park,
but in, like, we're in, like, the back rooms of it,
where it's, like, it's all, it's like,
it's kind of like a shopping mall sometimes.
It smells like, well, maybe it's a water park,
but it smells like green water.
Okay.
Ooh.
Yeah.
I don't know, did Mike part of it come up?
If anyone wants me to wash my hair,
they can send me shampoo and stuff, huh?
Their choice, but I have, like,
The shampoo conditioners are so powerful.
Sorry, but it's a nice kind of shit.
Not the one that you all that made it.
If you don't flowers.
Flowers.
Yeah, I'll watch those.
Have a nice day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, she, let me see.
Yeah, I was on camera at the time and now they have on my they said they think I'm stole they were like
He stole from the store. It was just yeah, they think I'm so because the lady yelled at me
Because I do a YouTube show. Oh, yeah
Yeah, so they put me on like they say oh he stole from the store. He shortchanged the store
It was just a misunderstanding with that with the
Yeah, yeah
Um, yeah, I just want to make sure that you know, it's okay. It's okay. Okay. Thank you. He's a good customer
I have two dollars cash, and then I'll put the rest of my car. Okay. Yeah
Okay, got it. Thank you so much
Okay, you heard her first
You heard her first. He said I did not steal and I'm a good customer
They were both very nice and concerned that I even mentioned it. He's like, well, why are you on tape?
I was like because I'm a YouTube show so it wasn't the chicken they yelled at me
That was the cashier that they though she was a cashier
She's like a younger nice person and I say and I love Asian people like I like I said my
Koreans
Is my brother I'm taught English in Korea and and he dated a couple Korean women there
Right and their families were like no white people. They did not like with people
They're like you're not marrying a white person. It's a married Korean person and so
And that's even, I wouldn't, it's also like, you know, Kim Jong-il or something like that, like the original one.
He married like this Japanese woman and she was like the lowest, considered like the lowest casting career of people.
Like these Japanese immigrants.
So it was kept secret that she was Japanese for a long time.
She was kind of like, she was beautiful, you know, she was beautiful.
Usually, I think that happens a lot in the world, like, you know, people change their,
change their, um, maybe I need to get married to, like, a wealthy, um, you know, European,
like, you know, monarch or something like that. Wouldn't that be interesting?
No. Actually, there's, um, there's this guy named Mark Harris, and he married this woman
named Martha Ray, and it's kind of like, it was, like, the guy that married Josh like a bore. It's, like,
They marry these like these much much much a little late the cops and a ladies screaming
I mean, then I sarcastically say I stole
Then the people believe it. I mean, it's like I wish I should I should have taught you guys another AI to be able to recognize AI
Like you can see
You know, that's a real picture of Mimi
That's a real picture of like, you know big trolla and whatever Sam puts up and then it's like it picks picks AI pictures of a
me like Hunter S. Thompson
You know, I'm not that bald.
I do have those glasses, but I'm not, like,
not, like, that bald.
I mean, it's like, my hair, my hair is, like, okay.
I mean, it's like, it's like, it can be better, right?
I can use it, but if I'm making a hair plug
or something, my hair, there's no gray in it.
There's not a gray in my face right now because of ours.
I spent my food budget, my McDonald's budget,
you know, where I'd be going there today.
I spent that on some re-calendars and energy drinks.
and, uh, bottle of coffee, still.
Hi, Nancy. How are you, sweetie?
Good to see you. Thanks for...
I'm sorry. I don't know if that, like,
that person bothered you in the chat the other night.
I don't know.
Like, I just want to make sure you're okay.
Everyone else is still mad about it, mad at me about it,
and I couldn't even apologize,
and so I want to make sure.
Thank you for being here.
I will, like, maybe make some more pretty little mods.
I don't know. I took away some people's mods,
You know, some people really haven't dropped me for one reason or another
Any exception of saying I'm trying to like, you know talk to summer or sometimes she's in every other chat
She's she knows I want to talk to her. She's having a great, you know
Fights recently with like, you know Mimi Christine and stuff, but uh
I've been texting her privately, but you know,
the other night I was texting her and it was like,
I don't know, I think, like just like,
it actually typed cutie and then I was trying to tell her
I didn't type cutie, but then it just said cutie again.
And so it's like, I look like someone weirdo.
So if someone's like, well, a summer,
he's like saying he's texting me cutie
and stuff, it was an accident.
What are they mad about?
Well, they're mad about, I guess,
some of them are mad about that Brandon Q was in the chat.
Some of them are mad about that, I guess,
There's another guy, not everybody, but a few people.
So that's someone that Kristine got into it.
I know that was a little bit sad, but, you know,
it's like some people's true colors come out.
Like, you know, it's like, because, you know,
Kristine's saying terrible things to her.
And then, like, we're getting like,
oh, I'm being so nice, I'm not saying anything.
Just saying, oh, someone should think
that summer has never had anyone's back.
Vita's saying that summer is like a grifter.
with her, with her charity work.
I mean, really, how can you be a grifter with charity work?
I don't understand.
Like, it's like, she gets donations,
she gives them to those people I know.
It's like, there's nothing,
like, Bita likes to make some kind of like,
you know, paint, some kind of smear.
And then she says, she says,
I, she was sure I'm doing all the kind of things.
I just ask questions about, you know,
what really happened because she hears bear, bear.
Okay, I'll be right back.
I'm gonna go in my house, go back, okay.
There's a shrub that's reached a giant stage
Started as a hedge about four feet tall
Now it blocks the sun and swallows all
Branches tangled thick as rope
Nobody can see the garden home
Birds moved in this bush
Needs a trim and needs a quick
But every man who goes inside
Comes out confused and traumatized
This is the case on a real song. It's pretty good actually.
Actually Mason loves the real version. Abida's Bush is a sensation, by the way guys, you
It's always on the front page whenever I go 39B as well.
I had it in just for a video on a day. Let me see.
Yeah, here it is. She says it's embarrassing, but I like the real song too, here.
Oh yeah, pre-girl right now. Hey, there's the north. What are you doing? You kissing?
You doing me kisses this morning? Yes? Yeah, where's the other cat? You saw the black cat?
You saw Tuxedos in the house? Tuxedo in here? Is he in the bedroom? He likes to sleep on the bed,
Oh, you're giving kisses. You give good kisses. Oh, you do good kisses. I mean, I've come to like,
like, yeah, there's Lenore. Beautiful Lenore. Oh, and where's Lola? Is Lola over here?
I'm just using my cats as props, right? You know, just tilly.
Like, they're, you know, they're very uncomfortable. They don't want to be on my lap or anything,
right? Yeah, look, that was Lola. Oh, there's Perrin. Here's Perrin today. They're gonna Perrin day.
Well, that means you're happy. You're gonna be happy with such a horrible owner as me, right?
Oh, you know, I'm such an abusive person, you know?
Did you hear her? She's being so loud.
You're lowkey.
She is very happy.
I was watching these funny...
Hi, babe.
There's these funny cat videos. Hold on.
I mean, I think it's like...
You know some of them, you know, I don't like hopefully the cats don't get her
But you know cats are like some arms clumsy and like little clutches and like little clowns in that way
I don't think it's like meant to be like harmful or anything
but um
Sometimes they might fall and stuff or like, you know, this would cap down the bath of it's up and
Start running around but some of these are hilarious. Oh, let me see. Let's see
90 seconds, but power
People say to get your cats concrete block
Oh my gosh. Fred, can you turn that off, please?
Yes. Oh my God.
Bring it square. I'm just trying to record my in-mots.
It worked instantly. I can't believe it.
You just saw there.
Dogs, like, stop with it. The dogs stop mid-airfroging.
Like, that worked. What the fuck was that?
Crazy. That'd be good for, like, you know, people that, like, are afraid of dogs and stuff.
And there was, like, dogs walking everywhere.
And then it's like, if they get, like, attacked, because they tend to get attacked.
They couldn't do that. It's like...
Okay, well that was crazy.
Anyway, I was just watching little stuff.
I don't know, do you want to watch a little bit more?
You were wondering, I know, what was that?
That was like, I thought time froze for a second.
Okay, we can look on rumble.
I don't know, do you want to watch like,
there's like fights, I don't know.
I mean, it's like, I'm not really going to show past episodes,
but Tripp kick his work, like his stuff is working,
not Tripp kick Tripp and Cipus, his channel,
Panelbers, VODs is back and running, it looks like.
Um, but those are like full episodes of shows, and so I don't know if those are
related to, oh Rudy's coming on, you're sneaking on Rudy, I know, I see
sneaking over here too. You're sneaking down Lenore? Oh, she knows you're there too.
She's very aware. She's just tolerant. She's tolerant. Hi Rudy. Hi Rudy, how are you?
Hi, hi babe. Okay, let's see what we got, let's see. Well this, I can play that, I mean this is,
You can see me fighting with Amanda, it's not very good.
Crystal Ambers is clumsy on my panel,
I can actually take some of that, it was boring.
My own panel is boring.
This is like, this is some of the kitty gang wars.
Let me see, let me see, I don't know.
Now we can see Rudy, he snuck in.
Hi, Rudy, you snuck over here?
Hi, oh, that's your meow.
I know it's called tamping, it's called tamping
when you tamp the pen.
I don't want, I don't, stop, stop taking your tampons
and making tea.
making rituals about me stop it I'm done with it I can see you doing it oh it's
called it's called red tea no it's not it's called menstrual fluid tea and
stop drinking it and making side packs about me stop it now I had enough it's
good someone knives in the chat what you're gonna kill me now you're gonna
kill me and you want my blue that's the next thing they want they want a male
That's the next thing they're gonna do. They're gonna they're gonna get my blood
Ghost I'm gonna mod you but the mod fee is $50 and my
Super chat or else. I'm gonna take it away from you
Okay, and the whip for women is free because they have menstrual fluid and they can kill me
No more you guys stop using your period blood on me. Please stop it
until I see a super chat ghosty it goes it's been six months I'm about to die
of starvation because you didn't know I was monetized again and you're too lazy
to get a cash out just can you can you please help me out a little bit like a
couple of bro out yeah I mean guys I'll just make you a mod you're doing it in
exchange for mod this promise not to kill me with your menstrual fluid do we
have a deal because you know that's not an appropriate way for my mom to talk to
Fill a punching balloon. What is it? What does that even mean? It's on
Having you agree with the deal
Are you are you Christine? Are you Christine?
The ex the ex-minister of fluid put in the ocean put in the ocean to anonymous person. No a big thing balloon
Someone high Katrina right away
What's the cutoff of virginity returns?
Can someone answer Aaron's question? I just don't I don't know the answer to that. I don't know the answer to that one
I'm kind of getting confused at this point.
A big thick balloon, right?
A big thick balloon.
You're sick.
You're one sick motherfucker.
You're a great mod though.
Thank you for being my mod.
Hey, it's menstrual fluid.
It's like you ever heard of a menstrual show
where they had the black face?
It's called a red face.
Sam Ayal is here now.
Sam Ayal, who is menstrual fluid?
We've summoned now, we've summoned the demon
of menstrual fluid.
Lilith actually is the goddess of semen
Samuel's the menstrual fluid is it kind of goes backwards into the occult
Sweetie's going oh
No, she is oh
my goodness
Is that why she's the such as the kind bitch? I mean, please
I cared this morning, you know, I posted a serious thing like okay
Well, I'm being there's definitely a smear campaign going on. It was nothing not like anything I've ever posted
Everything you post sounds the same, uh-huh.
Oh, you're so funny.
Everything you say sounds the same.
All your channel says looks the same.
It's all me.
Okay?
How about, like, have your own channel, show yourself on camera.
You bitch.
No?
Oh, no, no.
Oh, we're just like, oh, I don't even know anything about it.
Oh, my God.
He called me a bitch!
Oh!
Oh, my God!
I call him a bitch all the time, bro.
I don't know why he's mad.
I call him a faggot.
Why does he get mad?
I just call him a few times.
He calls me a bitch.
First of all, I'm allowed to say that word.
I have the F-A-G-G-O-T word pass, okay?
That's what you get when you're gay.
It's one of the little benefits you get
in your purse they give you.
They give you the pass, okay?
Gay lady?
You don't have the pass.
You have, what can you say?
I don't know. Whatever the fuck you're spouting out in Iranian profanity. I've heard all your words
Classic. I'm sorry. That wasn't a very good
Barcy. I just don't know Barcy
It means I mean dumb bitch in Barcy
I've heard all her things. This is why I clip you. So see if you're like, oh, I want to well
Let's see what you're really like because you're not like that AI photo. You're using bitch, okay?
Oh, but in the hospital. Oh, poor me. Well, obviously you're okay. Okay. I mean, it's like you're out of the hospital now
Okay, now I don't feel so bad. Okay, it's gonna make you survive. Whatever it was. And you know, I haven't spent time in the hospital
Oh, how about this? Good luck on getting that other channel back. By the way, I'm gonna see what I'm really like
How about just watch my show instead of like looking at clips of me on yours
Like these curia clips of you know, you know, some of them are best of moments and stuff. I mean, but
Oh, shocking. He said the n-word. You know how many times I've been called the n-word on the show?
I have the n-word passed too, okay? I have every pass. I've been called everything, okay?
If you get called it on a regular basis, you can use the word. So I'm allowed to use the word, okay?
Sandman can use it. I'm definitely probably blacker than him, okay? Got a problem with that?
Okay. I'm on camera. So you don't need to fucking play around with my image and all this shit. You
It's not a mystery.
Not using my high school, you know,
Bodo,
catch up with like AI, I'm not.
This isn't me.
I don't have bed bugs midnight.
Okay, you're getting timed out.
You think about what you said.
Like tarot card reading or anything else like that. She's a clipper. She does a short clipping channel
Happy endings. I'm not
So is what he's gonna do fine if he's gonna be a clipper
You guys just remember when you go there for intuitive psychic reading and you want to you know
Get memberships and you know be part of you know this great thing you're gonna be
uh, associated with, you know, harassment, bullying, uh, you know, kind of doxing a lot
of fucking doxing. If he had, if he had sweet peace information, I bet your ass it would already
be out there because he did it to me. Um, he doxed my fucking name. Last thing he put out,
you know, pictures of my ex that has nothing to do with this community. That's why I give him
the fucking strike and I could have even pursued it, but I'm just telling you, there's a difference
All of the pips, pips, pips and sips, uh, Sweet Pete, it's all for fun.
They take clips out of that whole, like, lives and they make a little short about it.
It's, it's not about the picture.
He can make whatever pictures of me he wants.
I could give a fuck.
I'm a grown person.
I don't care about cartoons.
It's about what he had to say. It's about the words that came out of his mouth.
And the people just enable his fucking shitty behavior.
And he's not going to be someone else next time.
It's just never going to stop. He's a piece of shit.
Anyway, that's all I have to say.
Yeah, because it does I mean it happened to me and it's happy it's gonna happen to me
It's like me and him have been going at it. It's non-stop
Christine the same thing the bullshit that he puts her to remind you
We can all just be like this is all like for ships and giggles, but he goes low Christine is a nurse
You know suffering from cataracts glaucoma or blurred vision
Did you know your eyesight can be afforded to one single without laser surgery or treatments?
No, it's not a myth.
A study conducted in our lab, independent of Big Pharma, has shown that vision problems are direct
Tell a nurse that you're actually doing the opposite of, you know, your job, which is saving lives.
It's a pretty fucking disgusting insult.
He's streaming right now, by the way. Sorry.
Do you guys know what she makes clips about me? I don't care. I sound smelly and goofy.
You think I like to hear myself singing like that, but hey, if it makes other people laugh,
you know, it's for fun.
But that thumbnail is not funny. It's not original.
You're absolutely like body-shaming, making fun of a person that you want to come up.
Why? So you can have their actual picture.
Yeah, and that's actually not gonna ever work if that's your end game.
to insult me just so I'll prove you're wrong that that's never gonna be a reason
right that's why he's getting you to try to know it's never gonna work I will
come up one day but it's gonna be on my terms whenever I feel like I want to
really have anything to say to you okay oh well I thought you were laughing at the
meme and also before an hour before the meme you posted me
at a window looking like a monster saying oh donations please and something that you
yeah it was a joke you said it was i you said you posted this that after me you lied sweet
you're drunk you lied you're drunk right now i'm not talking you lied lady
Okay. She's in the lights. Okay. I can't take it. Well, she don't want to talk to me. Okay. All right. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on
Talk so psyche was bring we all in good times panel this morning, and you said you're just gonna stop you're not, you know, okay?
Okay, I know I know I know I know I know I know I know but hold on
Hold on then but let me give you let me ask you this haven't you repetitively like said that it's okay for her to make
Shorts of you isn't she just like any other any other any other clipper?
She had a good sense of humor because she was like laughing and I was like, hey, she had a good sense of humor and it's funny, credentialed.
Sam and Bita, Christine, come look, he's saying this and this.
Nobody, no, no.
What is the difference between Sweet Pea and any other clip or like Bakelips, Janny, Tripp & Sip, Beep Beep.
You know, any of them, why are you so going hard on 3P?
No, I'm not sure why are you so going hard on 3P.
Is it because of me? Is it personal because of me?
No, it's because it's just me, CP and I, because she has also the bald clips of me
where it's actually using my shield image.
Which you said that you...
gave me permission to meet by the way. Sure, you do. Thank you. All of the all of the clippers they
always like make AI image like you know some of them might I look hideous some of them they make
me look better you do the same thing with you and some of them are like especially like let's
take trickle we love his we love his intro some of them you look funny some of them you look great
it's like all these are whatever so what is the difference between sweet peace like remember when
and make AI images of somebody and put it out there.
That's the difference.
You said it's bad luck to do that
and it puts like bad, you said something.
Of her is a cartoon.
Of her, it's my actual image.
Well, you may know well, like these fat bitches.
Bruh, Henry, those are people.
I'm gonna be quiet, you guys talk.
Cause go ahead.
Are you saying that you've never made AI images
of anybody else on this panel?
I really don't make a you want to think about that answer before you answer but but beta
But what I put a clown face on beta or I like it wasn't like insulting or anything, right? Oh, it's not insulting
But I'm gonna leave okay and
what
Okay, well never
No, that was weird
Wow
Oh, I didn't mean to interrupt you, but if you could get sweet, you're going to have to handle you, we're going to end it.
So what was that? What was that whole purpose of them coming here to Ragewood?
The only thing, Christian, the only thing 3P asked was making, putting like a clown face, that's like whatever, and that's funny.
And he didn't want to hear the truth. He just left, you know.
Ask look at him. Look at him. Yeah
This is the real person
Everybody want a reading from a really intuitive peaceful
Anybody want their fucking life goals to be in the right direction follow this guy
I don't know what he expects to gain from all this this back and forth dancer. I mean it doesn't solve anything. He's obviously upset beyond measure and he will not forgive. This is just the way. So what's the plan of coming over here and other people who just want the content out of it because it's funny to them is sick me to me because it's not it's not funny.
You know that's the problem Tracy he can act like see the a lot of tarot card
There's a lot of like scammers out there
Okay, there's some that actually genuinely do this and they want to help people
But would you want to go and see a reader you go subscribe to oh
Just the cult of whatever and then you see on a community post a picture of
Somebody being made fun of like you know that your focus is tarot card reading
But yes, you do nothing but fucking drama go at people scream at people that don't fucking like don't agree with your shit
Hold on. Let me see you with backstage, okay?
Money for each money. Hold up. You do all this fucking shit and then if you get called for you called out for it
You go, oh, you're hurting my income. You're hurting my income. Well do better than do fucking better
Sorry, I just wanted to say that hi money. What up beta? It's me
Entertainment, okay. I mean
You're the rage quick. If you know how to read cards make your fucking life better
How about a pull a card for yourself and tell you what direction you should go into Tracy?
Hi money money without sweeping Chris to trick with up everybody
How's it going?
Yeah, you slander everybody else, you slander everybody else like he and you run like a fucking bitch
And you rage quit to go into the chat. I swear. It's like groundhogs day fucking. I know. I know
It's the same old shit. It is a very repetitive day. Very repetitive. I mean look listen
Let me tell you an example last night. He man. You weren't there
He was on psychies. He was making the men feel so uncomfortable.
Tripp is like, Christine, can you come up here and help? I mean, come on.
And Tripp and Christine go back and forth on each other all the time.
He doesn't take no for an answer when it comes to shit.
You tell him to stop something, he goes even further.
You tell him to leave you alone, he doesn't leave you alone.
If you fucking try to negotiate with him, he just fucking makes excuses.
It's like the same fucking shit. I'm sorry, I don't know why I did that.
Alright, there we go. What do you want from this most site? What is the point? What do you want from this?
You can see this way come back
Okay, don't sit down you're sitting here. I mean yesterday you are making serious
16 I was 16. They're just trolling me to
Because you said the napalm thingy now they're just trying to fucking risk my channel by the stupid fucking comments like that you fucking idiot
Yeah, that's that's a biggie's boyfriend for you. He's on his second can of whatever he's drinking. So
I can drop so I want to move on I want to move on I want to move on about who's gonna be on the panel and how to run my
It's your it's your show. Okay, it's your show, but I just want to say if I offended anybody
I genuinely am sorry. I don't offend anybody of any race or any color nationality. I'm a gay person
You people say all kinds of shit about gay people. I understand discrimination. I understand all this stuff
I love these people actually and I put a lot of my heart when it comes down to it
I'm beyond all like the yelling and like the same bad things. I do love all you people
I do and it's like, you know
And I'm sorry if I hurt anybody's feelings and that all that
And he will okay. He will it's too many people that that's that's what he does
This is what he has his spiel is he's so entangled in this like fucking bullshit that that's what he does
You know, I mean you can it's one in one ear out the other, but I don't know who's being mod
I don't know who's being timed out. I don't know. I'm not on my monitor, but please you guys mods don't time out with your feelings
Okay
Four things to never do if you have stuck mucus and breathing problems.
You can't get the mucus to come out. I can fix that.
Trust me, I've done it. You don't have to live with it.
You can be breathing better by the end of the week.
You just need to fix the real cause, not the symptoms.
See, breathing problems aren't actually caused by your lungs.
It's this stuff in your chest.
Once we get it out, then your lungs will heal themselves.
Really. Yale researchers proved it.
They discovered one root cause behind most breathing issues.
And once you address it, your lungs can heal themselves naturally.
Here's a few things I tried and here's what worked and what did.
A nebulizer with saline solution.
All right.
This thing is a waste of money.
Trust me, I've tried this a thousand times.
Only the shit that's supposed to be like, you know, lies, disgusting.
I didn't think I had in the cat.
I was kind of like, I get upset sometimes.
But at the bottom of my heart, I do have love for everybody on the fan.
I do have love for you.
I like Crystal Anne, I like Bita.
I think they're good people.
Subscribe to them.
We didn't love them.
We don't, I don't need anyone.
You're on my panel.
What do you mean subscribe to them?
They're already subscribed.
You can get along with them.
Even that's wrong.
I try to be nice and that's wrong too, right, Bita?
Okay, person.
Yeah, it wasn't me.
I'm just saying, if anybody, you know,
because I have to time out some people that.
I know you're chatting constantly, Bita.
Constantly.
I didn't think you did, Christine.
I didn't say it with you.
Nobody said you don't I would just saying just in case I wasn't even saying I'm just saying you guys don't I wasn't saying anyone did
Okay. All right. It's always the second technicality
She can be up Samans panel today made him 20 bucks. Then he comes in
You know the clapping system. That's the way
When Samans wrapping up and says, oh, Peter, are you doing it live? And I say, I'm
Comes on the air and says, oh, I take 25 bucks for a psyche I'll take 20
Okay, well, I'll just I'll sleep look at him like look at how he gets so scared. Oh, come on. Come on. He doesn't even take a joke
He looks what I'm saying a little snowflake, but he takes it right here. No one's gonna laugh
But you will it's one sense 20 bucks. We think you're like what that's like your main issue is like getting
Nobody, no, I haven't kicked you off either. I'm just saying like look at him
I was like I mean jokes about fucking all kinds of shit. Uh, okay, you know psych's apologizing, right?
And and you go back on it. What's the what's the punishment go back on it?
If I ever apologize then it's like oh your apologies not genuine or you need to do this or that it's like never accepted
It's never like it's never like nothing is ever resolved. It's always
Okay, well, let's do it right now. Okay
No, see it won't be it's just like the same a lot of fighting lately. Yeah, there's some good
Christine versus summer yesterday, but you know summer of course one
Christine has to like make herself through the victims of all
Took off the background so you can see it look more better. Hi, Lenore. Give me kisses
Give me kisses who's the best cat in the world
Anyways um so we have a new channel intro that somebody made for me and I want to give
a really big special shout out to my friend.
Some of you know him as different things.
He goes by a few different things on YouTube but I think maybe you might all know him best
Tony or allied master computer. So thank you for the new intro. I appreciate it man. Here it goes
But thank you guys the new channel intro
I don't know what the video is about. I have no clue what the fuck is on the video
But I thought it looked cool and shout out to Tony for making that for me
This is original artwork by the way
That people tried to steal
I can't, that's all I have. I cut the video down because you don't need fucking two minutes
of the rest of the song. The first 50 seconds are enough. The intro was too fucking long,
Especially when you're restarting the stream every fucking five minutes, so most of the that motherfucker's streams were shorter than the intro like the actual stream itself is shorter than the fucking intro.
Most of them.
Right.
You think I can stick psyche up for 50 bucks for the intro.
Nope.
Hands up don't shoot.
Hey, Tony, if you're in here, yeah, tell fucking psyche to cash out 50 bucks and I'll abuse the intro. I'll abuse my intro.
That's too good.
Let me just say this to you niggas out there are lucky that I don't know how to do what Tony did because none of you would have channels
There wouldn't be no fucking Zaya. There wouldn't be no Peds. There wouldn't be no fucking Sam in there
Wouldn't be none of you niggas bro. None of you would exist if I had the power to do what Tony did the psyche
There wouldn't be a community anymore. I would wipe all of you out
Y'all are lucky. I don't know how to do what he did. So lucky. I would wipe the whole fucking shit out
There's whole fucking place gone zapped in a day
I do it all in one day, too
It'd be like it would be like fucking like the godfather part, too
You know when he go when everybody gets fucking whacked or is that in the first one?
It's at the end of the first one or it's the middle of the second one whenever he just goes and fucking lax everybody
That's what would happen
Yeah, Tony the conductor if I knew how to do what Tony did nobody around here would have channels like I would be
I'm way too fucking reckless to have that type of knowledge. Oh, I fuck everybody shit up everybody
Well, not everybody but the people that I really don't fucking like
Yeah, I would I would make sure that every time you fucking went live. I copyright struck it every time Benjamin Kowalski
You would know that fucking name. Oh man
You better hope to fucking God I never get that knowledge.
Second, second what?
That wall, you know what?
I'm not sure exactly if it is the same truth finder method.
And I know what that method is.
I don't want, I'm not going to say it
because I don't want to give too many of these people
like too many people, too many different ideas.
It's like, I know what the...
The process is technically like loosely, but I don't know how to actually make it work
You know because I'm not gonna go through all that bullshit and then fucking
Not even work, you know like go through filling out all that bullshit
And then by the time you get to the end of filling all of it out and do a quick thing that doesn't even work, you know
Yeah, I know how I mean
There's a theory. I don't think anybody knows a hundred percent
See, that's I don't know. I thought that the truth finder thing was
Was kind of like up in the air like people guessed what he did
But nobody really knew exactly how he did that like how he fucking just went and struck everybody shit
Like he got player one and all them like I don't know if anybody knows exactly how he did it
I think a lot of people have theories with different based on like uploading it to different websites
And then coming back to YouTube and saying gotcha
you know, because YouTube isn't gonna ask no questions.
And that's what these fucking idiots over there,
these stupid fucking retarded, middle-aged,
menopause-made-in fucking tarot hoes,
sitting over there telling him like,
hey, thank you, I just looked it up online,
and the copyright, you know, it says,
And they're going to say, well, this guy can't prove that he owns the copyright.
So we're automatically gonna give it to the one who's making the claim in the first place
But no, we have a bunch of these fucking 40 to fucking 55 60 year old women on here
That think that they know how this shit works. You don't know shit, bitch
You've had it you have fucking 300 400 sub channels and think all the sudden you know about how YouTube works
And you're trying to tell a nigga like me how this shit works. I've been monetized on the same channel for three years
No strikes. No, no, no private or no copyright strikes. No fucking community guidelines strikes. I mean, I've had them before but they're gone now, you know, they go away.
Nothing. Channel completely clean. Don't sit here and try to tell me how the fuck YouTube works, bitch.
Gonna try to tell me. Well, I looked it up on Google and copyright law says that you can't copyright an AI song.
Alright, well, why don't you fucking call YouTube and prove to them that it's an AI song? Because you can't. Nobody can.
Just because you say it's an AI song doesn't like YouTube doesn't fucking know that YouTube doesn't care to know that they don't give a fuck
They're gonna look at it. They're gonna be like, okay
We're awarding it to the claimer because the defendant in the situation can't prove that it's theirs either
Doesn't make very much sense. Oh
Guess what happens?
Psyche wakes up and he looks on his computer and what does Psyche see that all of the fucking the claims that he made got denied
Oh, oh
None of them were tonight mean to tell me that Christine in summer and fucking DJ
Electra aren't experts on copyright law especially when it comes to YouTube who would have fucking guessed who would have ever guessed
Can't believe it right amazing
So you know me as soon as that happened. I had to go back into that fucking bitch Christine's chat and be like
Told you bitch
Fucking old menopause bitches on here acting like they know something you don't know shit. No shit
Every smile, every look, every promise, a clothe
They were shaping the story before I could speak
The kingdoms of whispers were calling me weak
Come to the
Till your judgment breaks
On the silence while the pressure shakes now
It feels its name